I'll love you forever.
Buanga is really good at flirting.
No wonder, Thep head over heels in love with her.
So what are you going to do?
The lady gave you to be in this room.
Be in this room until giving birth.
If I'm not a public wife,
I would not dare to let the husband go far.
There is only beautiful people.
I've been here,
My house.
I would like to curse you all.
Let it be destroyed forever and ever.
Don't do this.
I sympathize and understand you.
But you don't have to exchange with anything like this.
I'm a teacher, you're a student.
I came to give knowledge.
Not to take anything from you.
And you need to get to her house?
She is very poor.
Her house is so poor.
Actually, she is an adult.
Should be able to find a lot of solutions.
She can use the computer at the university.
You also have a family to take care of as well.
Thep, this house ...
What's up, mom?
Should we go to the doctor?
I really saw.
I've always been wondering.
But what I saw today made me confident.
If there is a ghost,
And why did I never met?
It's probably not everyone who will meet.
Chicken curry rice.
I want you to try it.
Oops, suddenly itchy.
This is rash.
Buanga,
- Did you give the eggs to the lady to eat?
- I didn't.
- Are you kidding?
- Let me go.
- Aunt,
Can you see me?
Kem,
We used to know each other, right?
Who are you talking to?
Oh, I talked to a woman ...
Uh...
Want to know about it, right?
Is there a post box here?
Leave the house,
Turn left along the fence.
For 3-4 km, you'll be there.
Thank you very much, Uncle.
Any sweets?
Oh, the young man just moved to live here?
Your face is not familiar at all.
You,
Oh, wow.
Is this the girl who saved me back then?
That day, I was still not conscious.
So I haven't thank you yet.
Just seeing you look better, I'm happy.
Honestly, I wanted to send you to the house.
But if I and friends that day didn't rush, then we would missed the train.
Well, how was Hua Hin?
Swiming is very fun.
You and Thep should go.
We'll go all together. This must be very fun.
Yes,
Go ahead and eat.
Here you are,
See like I see?
Yes, I did.
- Oops,
- If this is really like this, will definitely get the eyes of the straw.
Oh, wow.
I already know who she look like.
Only worried about Luang Decha's, they may can't handle.
Ploy is smart.
The family is good.
As for beauty,
She've got it from me.
Who doesn't like her?
When Duangkaew first approached me, I was still hesitant.
Because he had never seen Thep before.
But now I see.
I fall in love with all my heart.
I wish I could have him as my son-in-law today.
What a guy.
The beautiful image of the angel.
Really handsome.
Ticklish.
Like when we were young.
- Going to work?
- Yes,
I come to ask for blessings from you.
Before I go to work on the first day.
May you have a clear brain.
In order to think of benefits to the nation, the country and yourself.
Whatever you do, it'll be easily accomplished.
Without enemies.
And no matter where you travel.
Please only have a lover.
Thank you, Father.
Is it for Buanga?
It's for the lady.
Nothing for Buanga.
(To my Buanga)
Why did she want to take it?
Can't read and write.
Take it away.
Tear out.
What's wrong with the car?
I don't know.
And where did you go in the morning?
You would not eat.
Khem,
Haven't received a letter from Thep?
There was one letter in the morning.
But the envelope address to the Lady.
How about you write a letter to Thep?
But I don't know the address.
Like that, must wait until Mr. Thep,
Come back home?
Buanga,
Walk slowly.
Address in Phra Nakhon?
I don't have it.
He didn't send a letter to me either.
We're on the same boat.
Staying here is a little better than being a servant.
Everything depends on the hand of the lady.
Do you have anything to tell me?
If it's about me, then just tell me.
I saw the lady torn this.
I can't read but when guessing that it may be yours.
I...
Mi...
Miss...
You...
And the baby...
A lot...
Now...
I work...
Partment...
What is the partment?
Partment...?
Love...
You.
Lady is worse than I thought.
Forget it.
Just knowing he missed me and my baby is enough.
Oh!
What?
Baby is moving.
That's bad.
So how can I be sure?
That the baby is my grandchild.
Despite letting she live in my house.
Even though she has bad intentions towards me,
I have shown it enough kindness.
Good, my lady. If you are more compassionate, you are God.
I was waiting for my son to know.
That she's not a good woman.
Is the baby is moving?
What's wrong?
Actually, the person who should be with me now.
Sigh...
Should be Thep.
He should be with me now.
Dear mother,
I've received the food that you sent for me.
But that made me miss our house.
I want to go back to you quickly.
But...
I'm just working for 2 months.
The Lord hired me to work,
Whatever I do, I must be more considerate of him.
Thank you mother,
For taking care of Buanga,
You can tell Khem to write a letter for Buanga.
Fortunately, I thought you would go home and evening like every day.
Aunt went to Chanthaburi, she bought you some fruits.
Thank you to the lady.
And what are you doing?
Oh, write a letter to the house in Songkhla.
Songkhla is very nice to travel.
If I go to south, can I stop by to visit your house?
You're really good at traveling.
Didn't Lady Prung said that you're good at housekeeping?
I never saw you cook.
I'm more good at eating.
But where are you going?
Dress up like foreigners.
Go to ride a horse.
My friend's house has many horses.
Do you want to go together?
I really do not agree.
You should know better than anyone.
That the house with more than one wife.
It's really not peaceful.
I want my baby...
To see father's face for the first time.
Sigh,
Oh, dress up.
Good.
What happened?
Mr. Mok's thing is missing.
Search the whole house but can't find it.
What?
Is there anyone left?
Is this?
Hmm...
Do you dare to steal Mr. Mok's bracelet?
The lady is kind to you.
Do you dare to do this much?
Found it?
Here you are,
- Well...
- You again.
Last time you thought of killing the Lady.
This time, you stolen thing.
Really the robber's traits.
I didn't really do it.
The other day I saw you go into the lady's room.
You must have gone to scout out the area.
I asked for Thep's address.
I swear...
I didn't do it.
I have never thought of Mr. Mok or everyone in this house.
If I really do, please die within three days and seven days.
I believe that Buanga didn't do it.
There must be someone to bully.
Are you daring to wonder me?
I let you live here.
Although you almost killed me.
Although your baby is not my grandchildren.
You still dared to wonder me.
Well, you believe that I am a bad woman.
Believemy baby is not your grandchildren.
So you find a way to eliminate me.
Dare to make a voice with me?
Buanga,
If it's this bad, then I don't need to care.
Please, Lady.
I've it back, I'm fine.
It's about the stolen.
But about its traits.
Not yet a daughter-in-law.
Still so brave like this.
Next, she won't care anyone.
Come, hurry.
Take her to imprison.
No need to see the light.
This is Mr. Thep's wife.
Khem, stop.
Otherwise, you will be punished.
Buanga,
Apologize to the lady.
Lady,
Please forgive her, she is pregnant.
She didn't feel normal.
Please.
I know what I am doing.
But if I didn't do anything wrong,
I will never apologize.
Take her away from me.
Go,
This is human.
Not a slave.
Not a pig, not a dog, how can she be imprisoned like this?
Why not?
Or should I send her home?
I won't.
I will wait for Thep here.
I know news from women who are in the same house as you.
So came to visit.
Ploy,
Then why did she go to the uncle?
Finally, we met.
Hello,
Well...
I came to ask for help from you.
I feel that there are other people at home.
Other people who are not human.
Put it on the front door.
Backyard.
And your bedroom door.
Yes,
But the young man who had been here, where is he going now?
He said that he was a descendant of the house.
Oh, Jomtab has ever been here?
But ... now he is in the hospital.
Other people who are not human.
Meaning a woman named Buanga, right?
I dreamed of her again.
This time clearly saw.
That I was with her in the house where I was now.
With Grandmother Mok, and...
And this woman.
Lady Duang Khae.
This is Thep's wife.
Khem, stop.
- Let me go with you.
- You can't.
I can remember my past lives, right?
If you can,
You probably saw everything.
The things that happened to you may have been
because she wanted you to see them.
Some things you don't see.
Because she doesn't want you to see.
It's not a coincidence, right?
Buanga is a person who curses my family.
And will come to take my life, right?
In the past, I thought it was not.
But now I'm not sure.
That,
What is that?
Today, I went to ask for a blessing for Jomtab.
The fortune teller then gave me a Yantra to put up for good luck.
I didn't know that.
You believe in this thing.
People can be changed.
Now, everyone did.
Is it delicious?
Try it, I do it myself.
Do you think this paper can do anything?
Today it looks quiet.
No wind but it's cold. I don't know.
Can you please stop meddling in other people's business?
Mind your business.
Forgive them.
You don't know what it they have done to me.
You haven't even born yet.
About the past life, let it end the past life.
Let's start a new life.
If it end, who will pay for me?
Don't mess with me.
There's only me who hasn't actually gone to school yet.
You took me to apply for school.
- I want to go.
- Yes,
But you have to wait for Jomtab to go home first, okay?
And when will he come back?
Today,
And I made an appointment for the doctor for you.
This afternoon.
I can't. I will have to pick up the Jomtab to go home.
Are you happy today?
So let's go.
It's late now.
Bye bye.
Hello mom.
Ploy,
You think you can escape me? You must receive karma that is commensurate with your evil deeds.
Today, I help aunt cook.
Are you sure that if I eat it, my symptoms won't get worse?
Definitely not because I just help to cut vegetables.
Eat now.
I'm sorry for taking you to hurt.
It's not your fault.
The horse doesn't like me.
How good is this? It didn't step on my body.
So you have to take leave of work for a long time.
I thought that I would go home next week, but I can't.
Ploy,
Can you do me a favor?
Try asking Thep.
As a fellow international student, he must have some knowledge.
I will ask.
But I don't really want to believe that someone will dare to do this.
The times are changing
The heart of the person changed.
The word "gratitude to the land" is no longer known.
Uh...
Is he better?
Tomorrow he can run.
Look,
Who does she look like?
You asked something that made no sense.
People with sprained legs need to rest for a month. How can he be better tomorrow?
Then what is that?
The letter that Thep want to send.
I would like to send to Duan Khae as well.
Buanga, it sing Nora all day and night.
So annoy.
This is really durable.
Even when her father came to get her, she still refused to return.
But it can be durable for so long.
Take this to Mok.
Said that secretly brought from my room.
Yes,
And what should I tell Mok?
Said that secretly brought from my room.
Yes,
In case there is anything more.
Buanga,
You should go back with your father.
Why will you be locked like slaves?
I know that,
If I leave this house.
I'll not come back here again.
And probably ...
Probably didn't see Thep again.
Buanga,
I heard this.
I changed my mind.
That I said that there is an important thing to tell.
I think it's better not.
Sister,
If it's something that I should know.
I heard that Thep is flirting with this woman.
Like this, so he would not go home
Calm down.
Don't be fussy.
If there is anything for you to help, hurry to tell.
I have to go.
Today, Buanga is strange.
It's unusually quiet.
Don't make a voice.
Or...
She will commit suicide.
Hurry and see it.
Yes,
Buanga,
Hmm here.
Are you going to sleep all day?
Why don't you wake up?
I said wake up.
Help,
- Aunt,
- Help,
Buanga,Buanga
- Buanga, help.
- What's wrong?
- Help,
What happened?
Mok,
Khem,
Why are you crying?
What happened?
I'm sorry.
I don't take good care of Buanga.
What does it mean?
Buanag is heartbroken that you have not returned.
So...
She's bleeding.
What about my baby?
I'' be with my wife and baby.
Buanga,
You don't hurry to leave me.
Why?
Why don't you wait?
I'm waiting for you.
Buanga,
Don't you love me and my baby.
No, no.
Help,
Buanga,
No,
Help,
Thep,
A nightmare?
Where are you going? Don't walk a lot.
I will go home.
Thep,
Wait to get well first and then go back.
I can't wait.
I'm worried about my wife and my baby.
Come and get some gourd casket to eat.
Not because of indigestion.
But because Thep, he already has a child, has a wife.
Calm down.
They didn't marry.
Have you already known?
Yes,
And why did you tell me.
You Let me fall in love.
Hey,
Well, I and my friend's, Duangkae, wanted you to get married.
And you're more worthy for Thep.
But they have children together,
they love each other.
Sigh,
I don't want to do it.
Mr. Thep,
Khun Luang.
Where are you going?
I will go to see you in Phra Nakhon.
What's wrong at home?
Buanga,
- Buanga,
- Mr. Thep, be careful.
What's wrong with Buanga?
Khem,
Why don't you send telegraph to tell me?
If I didn't come back,
I probably don't know how my wife and child are living or dead.
Can you hear that she gave the egg to me, she want to kill me?
You're bias.
Therefore you blamed everything on her.
And you have no prejudice against your mother?
Let's live our separate lives as I decide.
Let me go.
Ouch!
Mother,
- Duang Khae,
- Mother, mother
We are engaged.
If I didn't trust you too much.
I wouldn't have to suffer like this.
The fortune teller said that everything that happened was caused by a curse.
And what do you think we will do next?
I have to know first who is the curse of my family.
Said that you allowed me to get it.
I allow you to get it the house.
Uncle,
What's up?
Do you know that woman?
No.
Help,Help
Who is outside, please help.
Help,